<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Personal Experience - Category - Madame Dutykh Blog</title>
        <link>https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/categories/personal-experience/</link>
        <description>Personal Experience - Category - Madame Dutykh Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/categories/personal-experience/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Easter Mosaic</title>
    <link>https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/posts/easter/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Kateryna</author>
    <guid>https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/posts/easter/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h2 id="easter-in-abu-dhabi-is-like-a-mosaic">Easter in Abu Dhabi is like a mosaic.</h2>
<p>For some, it is a cultural occasion to gather; fot others, it is a quiet family day, a day of faith and church services. And all of this does&rsquo;not exclude each other - in fact, it coexists in a surprisignly harmonious way.</p>
<p>When you are surrounded by a different cultures, climate, and rythm of life, traditions become a choice rather than a default. They no longer live in the background of your surroundings but become a conscious act. In such an environment, you begin to feel more sharply: what in this holiday is mine, what can I bring from others, and what di I leave out. Especially now, when even within the same faith, church leaders are causing divisions and reshaping communities.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>A New Chapter in Life</title>
    <link>https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/posts/new_chapter_of_life/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Kateryna</author>
    <guid>https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/posts/new_chapter_of_life/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Wow!</strong></p>
<p>…this is one of our reactions to what we see in Abu Dhabi.</p>
<p>While the sense of novelty hasn&rsquo;t worn off, the colors are still vivid and the local nuances catch the eye with their distinctive features, I&rsquo;d like to share some surprising moments that caught me off guard:</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>My first experience of giving birth in Chambéry.</title>
    <link>https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/posts/first_giving_birth/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Kateryna</author>
    <guid>https://katerynadutykh.github.io/madamedutykh/en/posts/first_giving_birth/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h2 id="the-french-approach-to-pregnancy-and-its-management">The French approach to pregnancy and its management.</h2>
<p>In today&rsquo;s post, I would like to share my recent pregnancy and childbirth experience in Chambéry, France. I’ll skip unnecessary details, so this article is suitable for men.</p>
<p>One of the first thing that really caught my attention was how relaxed and natural the attitude towards pregnancy is in France — especially compared to the stories I’ve heard from friends and family back in Ukraine. Unlike in Ukraine, where the healthcare system often tries to &ldquo;save&rdquo; or &ldquo;preserve&rdquo; a pregnancy, here, it is not seen as something that must be controlled from day one.</p>
<p>A woman’s social life, as a rule, doesn’t change much. More often, until the end of the first trimester, doctors don’t take the pregnancy too seriously. I mean that everything is expected to go naturally, and unless the woman is in a truly critical condition, nobody will hospitalize her “for observation” at this stage. No special check-ups or hormone therapy are prescribed.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
